Aru-tes i-syen-ih-ne kln-ih-iz-eq koo-ja-i, "どんな时も大なな中间がいて" Anytime with important companions
Soh-nh iyon-eq koo-ja-i, "そしてあなたがいて" and then you
Ih=ef ef ef yu-tey-i; "Private is a good luck" I am really happy
Emerald seeds with buds and emeralds
Innocently smashed, dyed, smashed, covered with pure colors
Hurricane whispering whispers
Traveling guides guide the travellers who are far away
Transparency, sadness, sorrow, sorrow, sorrow, sadness
The heart is conveyed from the heart to the king
Thank you, thank you.
Ih=yen-yela soh-nh syen-sey-la; "ありがとうさようなら" Thank you goodbye
EX[cieran &amp;amp; linc-ala]; "ありがとうさようなら" Thank you, goodbye.
Lolosy tiria etolu tisia "ありがとうさようなら" Thank you goodbye
The miracle of the second dimension, the miracle, the miracle of crossing the dimension
The more imaginary, the more you want to cross the mind of the second dimension.
Heart rhythm and melody
Z-wang-n tor-on-eq a-wang-n earthes-re u-ja-n
(soh-nu ih=rate-la-n) (なんだか照れくさかったよ) (I don’t know why I always feel shy) [iyon-eq beg-jen-dai-nr tesm] [あなたが壊されてしまった时は] [When When you are broken]
Ih=ef vy-ela-i; "I am mourning" I am really sad dai... "だから" So
Ih=lac-ru-i von sho-nh sya-ion-i I am so happy that I am so happy that I am in tears.
The dark end of the 夕 る る る の 暮霭 暮霭 暮霭 暮霭 暮霭
The surface of the water is stained with colored glass on the surface of the glass.
The sky is staring at the night sky that is holding the starlight
A lot of fires and blazing lights
The other side is like a star shadow that descends from a distance.
If you don’t want to centrifuge, you will pass it to
Touring the world, patrolling the destiny, revolving, the world’s revolving life
The seven つ 満たし 満たし 満たし け け け け け け け け け け け け け
Ih=yen-yela soh-nh syen-sey-la; ありがとうさようなら Thank you goodbye
EX[cieran &amp;amp; linc-ala]; Thank you, goodbye.
Lolosy tiria etolu tisia ありがとうさようなら thank you goodbye